[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the southernmost capital city?", "correct_answer": "Wellington", "incorrect_answers": ["Perth", "Capetown", "Sydney"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The French fries are believed to have been invented in what country?", "correct_answer": "Belgium", "incorrect_answers": ["Norway", "Finland", "Denmark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What percent of movies released in theaters in 1985 were R-rated?", "correct_answer": "81%", "incorrect_answers": ["45%", "90%", "95%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the birth name of the star actress in the movie Sweet Home Alabama?", "correct_answer": "Laura Jeanne Reese Witherspoon", "incorrect_answers": ["Haley Reese Witherspoon", "Mary Andrews", "Emma Ann Witherspoon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Six countries are located along the Black Sea border. Which one among them has the longest Black Sea coast line (not including the Sea of Azov coast line)?", "correct_answer": "Turkey", "incorrect_answers": ["Romania", "Russia", "Ukraine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Wizard of Oz, the role of the Tin Man was played by Jack Haley but another actor was originally hired for the part. Who was this actor?", "correct_answer": "Buddy Ebsen", "incorrect_answers": ["George Burns", "Tony Curtis", "Don Knotts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Sixteen Candles, Molly Ringwald played the part of Samantha Baker. What actress was originally chosen to play that part?", "correct_answer": "Ally Sheedy", "incorrect_answers": ["Lori Loughlin", "Demi Moore", "Emma Thompson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The North Star, Polaris, is located within which constellation?", "correct_answer": "Ursa Minor", "incorrect_answers": ["Ursa Major", "Canis Lupus", "Canis Minor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country has more than 60% of worlds lakes due to its special drainage system.", "correct_answer": "Canada", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "Russia", "The USA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the motion picture, Thunderball, James Bond attends the fake funeral of this person.", "correct_answer": "Jacques Bouvar", "incorrect_answers": ["Antoine Simonot", "Emile Meyer", "Xavier Duval"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which European Union member has the greatest number of islands?", "correct_answer": "Greece", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy", "UK", "Denmark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which ody part of the human body can the Darwins tubercle be found in some individuals?", "correct_answer": "Ear", "incorrect_answers": ["Tongue", "Nose", "Eyelid"]}]